SHASHANK

ACHARYA

National University of Singapore

PHONE: +65 9051 1444 EMAIL: acharya.s@icloud.com LINKEDIN: linkedin.com/in/achsg

ABOUT ME

Computer Science freshman at NUS with experience in frontend web development, mobile application development, and graphic design. Team-oriented personality, but able to work independently as well, previously leading and developing various projects as a freelancer.

EXPERIENCE

AUG 2021 - PRESENT

NOV 2020 - JUL 2021

JUN 2018 - PRESENT

Tech Analyst | NUS Fintech Society

- Worked on a housing recommender platform with the Machine Learning Department
- Worked with Pandas, SKLearn, Tensorflow libraries to scrape data and train neural networks for housing recommendation.
- Created RESTful APIs using Flask to serve as backend.

IT Intern | Aptiv8 IT Solutions

- Proposal of new layout and functionality for the company website.
- Improvement of SEO and site functionality.
- Implementation of marketing automation system.
- Overall improvement in speed metrics (GTMetrix) from 51% to 86%

Web Developer | Freelance

- Led the redesign process for various companies' websites.
- Worked primarily with PHP, jQuery, MySQL, and Wordpress.
- Delivered improvements to site performance (SEO, Speed, etc.) to an average score of 84% on GTMetrix.

EDUCATION

BComp. in Computer Science
National University of Singapore

2021 - Present

International Baccalaureate

GIIS, Queenstown

Score: 42/45 with Higher Level Math, Computer Science, Physics, & Economics

2016 - 2018

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Swift	Python	PHP
HTML	CSS	JavaScript
Angular	React	Dart

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Xcode	MS Office	Adobe Suite
Docker	Postman	IntelliJ